你有一个看起来很棒的控件
So you've got a pretty sweet looking control, but what about
但是那些不能看到亮点的用户呢？Accessibility是建立一个应用，
users who can't see the shiny hotness? Accessibility is a key consideration
尤其是当你创建一个新的视图时重点考虑的因素
when building apps and particularly when you're creating new views. You
你可以从添加一个 contentdescription 开始，就像你将会在
can start by adding a content description, as you would for every
layout布局文件中的其他视图中做的一样，去确保它们都是可以访问的
other view in your layout, to ensure that they are all
但其他的，就像风速，航向
accessible. But what about views like our wind speed, and direction gauge,
还有那些并不是一成不变的内容呢？要知道
where the content isn't static? Knowing you're looking at a wind
如果你不知道它显示的风速和方向
gauge isn't very useful if you don't know what the speed and
而去寻找一个风速计是没有用的。好吧，这里有几个选项
direction it's displaying are. Well, there are couple
对于并不控制自己value的generic views来说
of options here. For generic views, which don't control
最简单的方法就是在应用运行时
their own values, this simplest alternative is to
设置 contentdescription
set the content description within your app at runtime.
而另一个可靠的方法是，每当可视内容被修改的时候
An even more robust solution is to send
从你的view中使用sendAccessibilityEvent函数
an accessibility event from within your view. Whenever the
发送Accessibility事件。然后重载dispatchPopulateAccessibilityEvent 函数
visual content has been modified. Then override the dispatch
和当前控件的可视的值
populate accessibility event, and then the current control's visual
继续吧，添加accessibility handler到你的视图中
value, the accessibility event. Go ahead and add accessibility handlers
当你完成后点击这里
to your view and then click here when you're done.